dditservices.com 2014-02-09

# Duodecad ITS

### Duodecad IT Services Luxembourg S.à r.l. (see our company contact details, hereinafter referred to as "Duodecad ITS") is committed to protecting your privacy. We take appropriate security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access, unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction.

»

Duodecad ITS hereby declares, that we never sell or rent the personal details provided on our websites to any third party or unauthorized person. We use the latest and most sophisticated security techniques to protect our member's private information.  
Duodecad ITS uses self-developed privacy protection programs to make sure that your personal details are always kept confidential.

»

Every transaction in our system is processed in a secure environment and the provided details are posted to the authorized recipients via encrypted channels. Note that [https://www.dditservices.com](https://www.dditservices.com/) uses similar security features to safeguard all the information posted on the website.

»

We will never send you any spam or promotional messages/emails. The provided details will not be used for promotional purposes. In accordance with all applicable laws and regulations, Duodecad ITS will send you automated emails to report the status of your transaction(s) made on any of our websites.

»

To ensure the protection of your credit card details, we never store them on our servers, thus making it impossible for hackers to obtain them.

»

We will never ask for your password. Please do not give out your login details to anyone who might compromise your membership.

»

Duodecad ITS may collect limited non-personally identifying information that your browser makes available whenever you submit one of our online forms. This information we collect may include your Internet IP address, the time and date and your browser configuration. This feature has been introduced to help identifying our customers, which may speed up the response time of our Customer Service department.

»

Please never send your full credit card number and CVC/CVV (last three digits on the back side of your card) to anyone by email. These details should be provided on secure payment platforms only.  
If you would like us to locate your transactions, please send us your card number's last 4 digits only, as it is required on our Transaction Finder form.

»

By entering the site, the visitor agrees to accept small, specialized text files (a.k.a. cookies) on its device from [https://www.dditservices.com](https://www.dditservices.com/). These files help the visitor's web browser to load faster after the initial visit and allow to customize his or her user experience (functionality cookies), necessary to execute the user's requests of navigating to certain secure pages (strictly necessary cookies), and track the user's navigating habit to anticipate his or her needs (tracking cookies). [https://www.dditservices.com](https://www.dditservices.com/) shall never distribute third-party cookies, or any other forms of malware (such as spyware or viruses) toward its visitor's hardware. It is possible to refuse the cookies any time by adjusting the appropriate browser settings, although such action may affect optimal user experience.

### Changes of the Privacy Policy

To guarantee perfect protection and satisfaction to our members, occasionally we need to update our Privacy Statement, reflecting the changes in our services. Changes of the Policy will be indicated at the top of the page showing the date of the last update.

In case material changes are enacted, the update will appear on the website prominently to implementing the change.

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail or see our company contact details.

If you do not want to receive marketing e-mail or other mail from us, please go to Contact us and choose "I do not want to receive marketing e-mails." and enter your details.

Back to the top
